# John Lee

#### SENIORFULLSTACKENGINEER

John has a bachelor's degree in software engineering and has been a Full-Stack developer since 2015. As a big crypto enthusiast, he decided to fully focus on blockchain development. He already has big experience with dApps creation where most of them were built using Ethereum (public or private network). Kai is a great team player and takes time understanding projects and delivering them in the best way.



codebeast0420@gmail.com

. +1 323 505 9909

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Lead Web3 Engineer CryptoDragons.com

07/2021 - 01/2022

• Wrote Smart Contract for ERC721 Tokens, ERC20 Tokens for minting Crypto Dragon Eggs, Warriors, Marketplace. • Built the back-end for handling the white list members and integrated the Merklee tree structure. • Demonstrated wallet generation, ether and token transfers, balance checks, and listening for events. • Interpreted the Invision design into mobile-first responsive front-end UI. • Redesigned the websites from scratch using create-react-app and custom Webpack configuration

### **Blockchain Architect and Engineer** CryptoDragons.com

07/2017 - 02/2021

• Created and deployed the EPT ERC20 smart contract to the Ethereum blockchain. • Created a set of smart contracts for the vesting plans of the company's investors. • Deployed and managed the token vesting smart contracts that lock investors EPT holdings for a particular time and allows them to regularly release part of the entire fund.

#### **Lead Blockchain Engineer** CryptoTax.io

05/2015 - 02/2017

• Provided the client with a full-functional back-end engine, smoothly integrated with rich front-end endpoints. • Implemented features including tax report fees calculation for different operations (trades, deposits, withdrawals) and coverage of the most frequent crypto assets use cases (stacking, lending, ICO, hard-fork). • Ensured that the first release of the production application went smoothly.

#### Senior Front End Engineer Cropper.finance

05/2014 - 02/2015

• Developed a Vue/Vuex app from the ground up. • Introduced state-ofthe-art technology and stable technology into a new project. • Architected the app structure, including the front-end codebase, frontend API proxy and server, deployment pipeline, and CI. • Worked alongside the CTO, introducing best practices, robust solutions, to all aspects of the app, from UI/UX to API communication and authentication.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML & CSS Angular Python

### **LANGUAGES**

English Limited Working Proficiency Chinese

Full Professional Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Swimming

Video Game,

Reading

Martial Art

## **EDUCATION**

#### Study Program The University of Tokyo

04/2010 - 04/2014

Courses

Computer Sciense